Jane and Fred are tired at night.
They eat dinner together at seven.
Their son eats dinner with them.
They relax and watch TV together.
Their son watches TV, too.
They put their son to bed at eight.
Jane has a hot bath.
Fred has a shower and brushes his teeth.
Jane reads a book but falls asleep.
Fred also falls asleep soon after.
Here is the same story told in a different way.
Fred and I are tired at night.
We eat dinner together at seven.
Our son eats dinner with us.
We relax and watch TV together.
Our son watches TV, too.
We put our son to bed at eight.
I have a hot bath.
Fred has a shower and brushes his teeth.
I read a book, but fall asleep.
Fred also falls asleep soon after.
One: Fred and Jane are tired.
Are Fred and Jane tired?
Yes, they are tired.
Two: They eat dinner at seven.
Do they eat dinner at six?
No, they do not eat dinner at six.
They eat at seven.
Three: They have a son.
Do they have a daughter?
No, they do not have a daughter, they have a son.
Four: Their son watches TV with them.
Does their son watch TV?
Yes, their son watches TV with them.
Five: He goes to bed at eight.
Does their son go to bed at nine?
No, he goes to bed at eight.
Six: Jane has a hot bath.
Does Jane have a shower?
No, Jane doesn't have a shower.
She has a hot bath.
Seven: Fred has a shower and brushes his teeth.
Does Fred brush his teeth?
Yes, Fred has a shower and brushes his teeth.
Eight: Jane reads a book.
Does Jane read a book?
Yes, she reads a book.